你答应要嫁给乔伊
You said you'd marry Joey?
你要知道我当时可是累坏了
Okay,you have to realize,I was exhausted,
很情绪化
I was emotional.
任何人求婚  我都会答应的
I would have said yes to anybody.
就像上次你向我求婚一样
Like that time when you and I got married.
我控制不了自己
I'm not helping.
你才刚生下我们的小孩  却答应要嫁给他
So you said yes to him,and you just had our baby?
没错  而且按照习俗
That is right. And traditionally,
父亲应该要送母亲一个礼物的
the daddy gives the mommy a present.
但是我不打算跟你计较
But I am prepared to let that go.
所以当我过来看看
So when I came here to see
你是否愿意重新来过
if you wanted to maybe start things up again..
你已经跟我最好的朋友订婚了
you were engaged to my best friend?
是吗
Really?
我以为钱德勒才是你最好的朋友
I thought Chandler was your best friend.
钱德勒是我的老朋友
Well,Chandler's my oldest friend.
乔伊是我的  不
Joey's my.. No!
嘿  我要走了  进来说一声再见
Hey,I'm gonna take off. I just wanted to say goodbye.
瑞秋答应要嫁给你
Rachel said she'd marry you?
我走错房间了  不好意思
This isn't the right room. Sorry,folks.
好吧  我不想否定你
OK. I don't want to be negative.
所以我要说你挑的标语大部分都是很棒的
So I'll say most of the signs you bought are good.
不  "恭喜生女儿"的标语卖完了
No,they ran out of "It's a Girl!"
但是我可以处理一下的
But I can fix this one.
瞧怎样
See? Huh?
真性感
So sexy.
-亲爱的  -什么
- Honey? - Yeah?
亲爱的  你何不去躺下休息呢
Honey,why don't you lie down?
不不不  没关系
No, no, no. It's okay.
罗斯跟瑞秋很快就要回来了
Ross and Rachel will be back soon,
然后我得去办公室
and then I gotta go to the office.
是从我嘴里长出来的吗
Am I producing them?
你为什么这样累呢
Why are you so tired?
我昨晚无法入睡
I couldn't sleep last night.
我很担心
I started worrying about
今天的大型部门会议
this big divisional meeting I have later today.
我越是担心  越是没有办法入睡
The more I worried,the more I couldn't sleep.
你知道的  我会想
You know,and then I was,like,
如果现在睡着  我顶多睡六小时
"If I fall asleep now,I'll get six hours' sleep.
但是如果我现在睡着
But if I fall asleep now,
我顶多睡五个小时
I'll get five hours' sleep."
无论我怎么试  就是睡不着
No matter what I did,I couldn't fall asleep.
你知道你应该做什么吗
You know what you should've done?
对你自己讲那个小故事
Told yourself that little story.
-欢迎回家  -嗨
- Welcome home. - Hi.
标语是菲比做的
Phoebe did the signs.
你们  真是太谢谢你们了
You guys,thanks for doing this.
瞧瞧大家送来的礼物
Look at all that stuff people sent.
噢  天啊  这正是每个母亲所需要的
Oh,my gosh. Look,there's something every mother needs.
一个挤爆整间公寓的大黑猩猩娃娃
A giant,stuffed gorilla that takes up the entire apartment.
真搞不懂有些人在想
What are people think..?
你们送的呀  我真是太喜欢了
You guys,I love it.
嘿  罗斯在哪呢
Hey,so where's Ross?
他在楼下把东西搬出计程车
He's downstairs getting the stuff out of the cab.
他还在气我们两个吗
Is he still mad at us?
气你多过气我
Well,you more than me.
他总不能太生我的气
But he can't stay too mad at me.
我才刚生下他的小孩耶
I mean,I just had his baby.
太不公平了  我又不会生
That's not fair. I can't do that.
我不知道他上来时 你应不应该在场
I'm not sure you should be here when he comes up.
那正是我所担心的
Say that's what I was afraid of.
我也不认为我该在场
I didn't think I should be here either.
但某人说罗斯现在该已经释怀了
But somebody said he'd be over it.
嘿  我怎么会知道呢
Hey,what do I know?
我只想买个更大一点的黑猩猩
I wanted to get a bigger gorilla.
我们在芝加哥
The numbers we're seeing in Chicago,
纽约  以及伦敦的业绩都很扎实
New York and London are solid.
但是我们许多分公司的业绩却呈现衰退
But many of our field offices have reported disappointing yields.
波士顿衰退  亚特兰大衰退  休士顿衰退
Boston is down. Atlanta is down. Houston is down.
我可以一直念下去
I could go on and on.
但是为了不让你们觉得无趣
But instead of boring you..
我直接说明我的42点计划好了
I'll go straight to my 42-point plan.
沃特
Walter.
她真是太可爱了
She's just so cute.
我真想咬下她的耳朵  当成糖果一样吸
I just want to bite her ear off and use it as a sucking candy.
菲比
Phoebe.
但是我可以把这些小脚
But I could take one of those little feet
放到面饼里面
and put it in a pita pocket.
好了  我把大部分东西都放好了
Okay. I put most of the stuff away.
噢  太好了  奶嘴呢
Oh,great. The pacifiers?
在柜橱里
It's in the cupboard.
-打嗝围兜呢  -毛巾橱里
- The burping cloths? - Linen closet.
尿布呢
The diapers?
在医院
In the hospital.
哇  你们有间医院吗  真酷
Wow,you guys got a hospital? Fancy.
不  我把尿布忘在医院了
No,I left the diapers at the hospital.
在袋子里面还有一些
There's some in the bag,
但是我现在就出去多买一些
but I'll run out and get some more.
好的  谢谢
All right,thanks.
经过咖啡屋时可以帮我买个松饼吗
Could you stop at the coffeehouse and get me a muffin?
-当然  什么口味的 -让我想想
- Sure. What kind? - Let me think.
我要什么口味呢
What do I want?
请你慢慢想
Please,take your time.
那真是非常重要的决定  不像是
It's an important decision,not like..
决定要嫁给谁那样简单
say,I don't know,deciding to marry someone.
那可是事关松饼噢
This is about a muffin.
-蓝莓的  -好吧  蓝莓
- Blueberry. - Blueberry it is.
谢谢你
Thank you.
哇  他还在记恨  对吧
Wow,he's not letting this go,is he?
天啊  你觉得这会持续多久呢
God,how long do you think that's gonna last?
我不知道
I don't know.
他倒是对"我们当时分手了"那件事
He got over the "We were on a break" thing
释怀的挺快的
really quickly.
算了  我现在没空去操心那事
You know what,I can't worry about it right now.
因为我有了这个可爱的小宝贝
Because I've got the cutie little baby.
我无法相信我是如此爱她
I can't believe how much I love her.
我是说  我太爱她了
I mean,I can't get enough of her.
就像现在  我好想她 我真的好想她
Like,right now? I miss her. I actually miss her.
话说  她就在这里
You know,that's her?
天啊  瞧她睡着的样子  我好爱她
God,look at her sleeping. I love her so much.
-我要把她吵醒  -瑞秋  不要
- I think I'm gonna wake her up. - Rach,no.
你千万不要吵醒熟睡的婴儿
You know,you're never supposed to wake a sleeping baby.
我高兴怎样就怎样  她是我生的
Well,I can do whatever I want. I made her.
来吧  小宝贝  嗨  艾玛  嗨
Come on,little girl. Yes. Hello,Emma. Hello.
我想说我早就警告过你了
Well,I would say I told you so,
但是她已经帮我说了
but she's kind of doing that for me.
我很抱歉  妈咪很抱歉 再睡吧
I'm sorry. Mommy's so sorry. Go back to sleep.
再睡觉吧
Go back to sleep.
-哭得真令人心碎  不是吗  -没错
- It breaks your heart,doesn't it? - It really does.
你认为我们还要呆多久
How long do you think we have to stay?
好了  如果大家都同意  那就定下了
Okay,if everyone's onboard,it's settled.
钱德勒
Chandler?
-钱德勒  -在
- Chandler? - Yeah.
你同意吗
Are you onboard?
是的
Yes.
那么问题就解决了
Well,then problem solved.
钱德勒会负责我们在塔尔萨的办公室
Chandler will run our office in Tulsa.
你会喜欢俄克拉荷马州的
You're gonna love Oklahoma.
好了  我们已经喂过她了
All right. We already tried feeding her,
换过尿布  让她打嗝了
changing her,burping her..
试试看这个
Try this one.
时光倒流  听取菲比的警告吧
"Go back in time and listen to Phoebe."
-好了  试试看这个  -什么
- All right,here's something. - What?
上面说试着把婴儿抱起  贴近身体
It says to try holding the baby close to your body..
然后快速地左右摇
and then swing her rapidly from side to side.
好的
Okay.
太有效了
It worked!
不  只是让她吐了一点奶
No. Just stopped to throw up a little bit.
莫妮  我该怎么办呢
Mon,what am I gonna do?
已经好几个小时了  它就是哭个不停
It's been hours,and it won't stop crying.
她  瑞秋  不是它  是她
She,Rach. Not it. She.
是噢  我可不太确定了
Yeah. I'm not so sure.
噢  我的天啊  我快疯了
Oh,my God,I'm losing my mind.
是啊  说得没错
Yeah,no kidding.
好吧  这刚好证明
All right,this just proves
跟罗斯做爱  绝对没有好事会发生
no good can come from having sex with Ross!
嘿  甘瑟  我要外带几个蓝莓松饼
Hey,Gunther. Can I get a couple of blueberry muffins to go?
-尿布  是吧  -是的
- Diapers,huh? - Yep.
我猜瑞秋生下你的小孩了
So I guess Rachel had your baby?
-是啊  你能相信吗  -不能
- Yep. Can you believe it? - Nope.
首先我就不能相信她竟然会跟你上床
I can't even believe she slept with you in the first place.
你的意思是
You mean,like..
罗斯  我知道你生我的气
Ross, I know you're pissed at me,
但是我们必须谈一谈
but we have to talk about this.
事实上  没必要
Actually,we don't.
好吧  但是我必须说
Fine. Okay. But I gotta say,
严格说来  我并没有做错什么
technically,I didn't even do anything wrong.
什么  你并没有做错什么
What? You didn't do anything wrong?
-我是说严格说来  我是无心的  -好吧
- I said I didn't technically. - Okay.
我们暂时不说你"一不小心"
Let's put aside the fact that you "accidentally"..
捡起我祖母的戒指
picked up my grandmother's ring
然后又 "一不小心"向瑞秋求婚
and you "accidentally" proposed to Rachel.
我可以先打断你一下吗
Can I just stop you there for a second?
当别人做这个动作时
When people do this:
我真的不知道是什么意思
I don't really know what that means.
你刚刚说什么
You were saying?
我尚可以理解你为何没向瑞秋解释
And I could even understand that you couldn't tell Rachel.
但你为什么没告诉我呢
But why couldn't you tell me?
你有一整天可以说  你却没有
You had all day to,and you didn't.
我知道  我应该说的  "我很抱歉"
I know. I should've. "I'm sorry."
你用错场合了  乔
Not using it right,Joe.
"我很抱歉"
"I'm sorry."
-我要走了  -不  别这样
- I'm gonna go. - No,come on.
听着  罗斯  我们必须解开这个心结
Look, Ross,we have to get past this.
把袋子给我
Give me the bag.
不  我不知道还能怎样
No,I don't know what else to do.
-我已经道歉了  现在  -乔伊
- I said I'm sorry,now.. -Joey
现在你应该对我吼叫  咒骂  或是打我
Now you should scream at me or curse me or hit me.
我不会打你的
I'm not gonna hit you.
为什么不打
Why not?
你会比较好过  我也会比较好过
You'll feel better. I'll feel better.
你心里清楚你想打我
You know you want to,
我从你眼中看得出来
I can see it in your eyes.
-我不想  -有一点想
- I don't. - A little bit.
-不想  -有一点
- No. - Little bit.
-不想  -多一点了
- No. - A little bit more.
-把袋子给我  -不  打我
- Give me the bag. - No. Hit me.
-把那个袋子给我   -打我
- Give me the bag. - Hit me.
-给我袋子  -打我
- Joey, Give me the bag. . - Hit me.
-我不是开玩笑的  -打我
- Joey, I'm not kidding.  -Hit me.
-不  -打我  打我  打我
- No. - Hit me. Hit me. Hit me!
你闪开了
You ducked!
我很抱歉  那是本能反应
I'm sorry! It was a reflex!
噢  天啊  真的好痛
Oh,my God! This really hurts!
我忍不住就闪开了
I couldn't help it.
当有拳头要打上你的脸 你会闪啊  瞧
When a fist comes at your face,you duck. Look.
你是怎么回事
What is the matter with you?
你该本能地闪开才对啊
You were supposed to duck!
为什么你没闪呢
Why didn't you?
我们去医院的路上再谈
Let's talk on the way to the hospital.
好啊  或许等到了医院
Good. Yeah,maybe while we're there,
可以让医生检查一下你的反射神经
they can check your reflexes.
-再喂她看看  -我已经喂过了
- Try feeding her again. - I already fed her.
我知道  所以我说"再"
I know. That's why I said,"Again!"
姐妹们  我们不可以窝里反  好吗
You guys,we can't turn on each other,okay?
那正是她想要的
That's just what she wants.
我们可以到外面谈谈吗
Can I talk to you outside?
不  你们待在这里好了
Oh, no, you guys just stay here.
我要去检查她的尿布
I'm gonna check her diaper.
菲比  你要不要一起来呢
Phoebe,you want to come?
他们要谈的事与我也有关
I'm kind of part of this.
事实上  小菲
Actually,Phoebs,
我们是要谈夫妻两人之间的事
it's a husband-and-wife kind of thing.
我就知道我该嫁给钱德勒的
I knew I should've married Chandler.
-好了  什么事  -好的
- Okay,what's up? - Okay.
我们曾经讨论过
You know we said
如果能搬到巴黎  住一年一定会很棒
it would be fun to move to Paris for a year?
你可以学习法式烹饪  我可以写作
And you could study French cooking,and I could write..
我们可以在塞纳河畔野餐
and we could picnic along the Seine,
去波尔多品酒
and go wine-tasting in Bordeaux.
-是啊  -很好
- Yeah. - Okay.
你知道有些人说塔尔萨
You know how people say that Tulsa.
就像是俄克拉荷马州的巴黎吗
is the Paris of Oklahoma?
什么  是谁说的
What? Who says that?
那些从没去过巴黎的人说的
People who have never been to Paris?
到底是怎么回事
Well,what's going on?
我们要搬去塔尔萨了
We're moving to Tulsa.
-你说什么  -好吧
- Excuse me? - Okay.
麦肯纳小姐  也就是我上司的上司
Ms. McKenna,she kind of works above my boss.
她要我搬到塔尔萨
She asked me to move to Tulsa
去当那边分公司的总经理
and be president of our office there.
我当时正在打瞌睡  迷迷糊糊就答应了
And I was sleeping and apparently said yes.
俄克拉荷马州的塔尔萨
Tulsa,Oklahoma?
先锋之州
The Sooner State.
管他是什么呢
Whatever that is.
钱德勒
Chandler,
我连歌舞剧《俄克拉荷马州》 都不想看
I don't even want to see the musical Oklahoma.
不是吧  "噢  美妙的早晨"
Really? "Oh,What a Beautiful Morning,"
"挂着流苏的萨里马车"
"Surrey With the Fringe on Top"?
你是在说我们要搬去俄克拉荷马州
Are you trying to tell me we're moving to Oklahoma
还是说你是同性恋
or that you're gay?
好吧  那些都没关系
All right,not that this matters,
但至少他们有帮你大幅加薪吧
but did they at least offer you a huge raise?
没有  但是他们会帮我们租一辆福克斯汽车
No. But they are going to lease us a Ford Focus.
-我会试着脱身 -谢谢
- I'll get out of it. - Thank you.
-艾玛是怎么了 -她误会了
- What is wrong with Emma? - She misunderstood.
她以为是她要搬到塔尔萨
She thought she was moving to Tulsa.
请问您现在有空吗
Ma'am,do you have a minute?
我有些坏消息
I kind of have some bad news.
我想我不能去塔尔萨了
I don't think I can move to Tulsa.
-什么  -事实上  说起来有些好笑
- What? - It's a funny story,actually.
我在今早的会议上睡着了
I kind of fell asleep in the meeting this morning.
所以当我说我可以搬到塔尔萨时
So when I said I'd move to Tulsa,
我根本不知道我在说什么
I didn't really know what I was saying.
你睡着了
You fell asleep?
但那是因为我整晚
But only because I was up all night
为会议担心而失眠
worried about this meeting.
是不是很好笑呢
Isn't that funny?
很讽刺  不好笑是吧  好吧
Irony. Not a fan? All right.
好吧  事情是这样的
See,here's the thing.
我回家告诉我老婆塔尔萨的事
I went home and told my wife about Tulsa,
但是她不想去
and she won't go.
至于我  我爱死塔尔萨了
See me,I love Tulsa.
塔尔萨是天堂  塔尔萨是意大利
Tulsa is heaven. Tulsa is ltaly.
求你别逼我搬去那里
Please don't make me go there.
-钱德勒  我 -我知道你很不高兴
- Chandler,I.. - I know that you're upset..
听着  凯萝  我可以叫你凯萝吗
No,look,Carol. Can I call you Carol?
我真不应该  因为你的名字是依莲
Why would I when your name is Elaine?
你儿子的照片真好看  雄壮威武
What a great picture of your son. Strapping.
是你女儿的照片  对吧
That's a picture of your daughter,isn't it?
她真是甜美
Well,she's lovely.
我喜欢有坚毅下巴的女孩
I like a girl with a strong jaw.
我会从塔尔萨打电话给你的
I'll call you from Tulsa.
嘿  情况如何
Hey. So how is it?
-我的拇指断了 -你的拇指
- I broke my thumb. - Your thumb?
真是奇怪
That's weird.
你确定你出拳的方式是正确的吗
Are you sure you're punching right?
握拳
Make a fist.
或许等一下好了
Maybe later.
罗斯  我觉得很糟糕
Ross,I feel terrible.
你可以走了
You know what,you can go.
我只要填一些表格就可以了
I just have to fill out some forms.
需要我帮忙吗
You want me to help you with that?
怎么  看起来像是
Why,does it look like
没办法使用我的畸形爪子吗
I'm having trouble with my misshapen claw?
姓名
Name?
不  我知道是罗斯
No,I know Ross.
但全称是什么呢
But what's it short for?
比如  像是罗素
You know,like Rossell.
或是罗斯托弗
Or Rosstrophor.
就是罗斯
Just Ross.
好名字
It's pretty.
-好了  生日呢  -你知道我生日的
- Okay,date of birth? - You know my birthday.
当然
Sure.
五  九月
May.. tember?
-十月十八日 -职业  恐龙
- October 18. - Occupation? Dinosaurs.
事实上我是古生物学  恐龙也可以啦
Actually,I'm a paleon.. Dinosaurs is fine.
画图可不行
The drawing is not.
好了  紧急联络人是谁呢
All right,who do you want as your emergency contact?
-瑞秋  我想应该是吧  -好的  关系呢
- Rachel,I guess. - Okay. Relationship?
天啊  关系复杂要写上半天呢
Boy,this could take a while.
-写室友 -少来了
- Just put roommate. - Come on.
你们比室友还更进一步
You guys are more than that.
你们要在一起了  不是吗
You're gonna get together,right?
我不认为我们将要在一起
I don't think that we are.
但是你们两个注定是要在一起的
But you two are supposed to be together.
我也这样想过
Well,I thought so too.
但是她却答应要嫁给你
But then she said she'd marry you.
别这样  罗斯  那根本没什么
Come on,Ross,that didn't mean anything.
她当时刚生完孩子
She'd just had the baby.
很恐惧要独自承担未来的重任
She was freaked out about doing it alone.
任何人求婚  她都会答应的
She would have said yes to anybody.
是啊  她也是这样说的
Yeah,that's what she said.
所以呢
So?
所以我不想做一个随便的存在
So I don't want to be just anybody.
其实  现在这样也比较好
You know what? It's better this way anyway.
我不知道我在想什么
I don't know what I was thinking,
再回到之前的关系
going down that road again with us.
如果我们只是一起生养孩子的朋友
It's just much easier if we're just friends
一切要简单得多
who have a kid.
-真的吗 -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
你可以接受那样的关系定位吗
And you're okay with that?
是啊  那本来就是我们的计划
Yes. That's what we always planned.
如果你有计划  就应该照计划执行
And if you have a plan,you should stick to it.
那就是计划的意义  不是吗
That's why they call them plans. Hello?
我没事的
I'm fine.
嘿  不管怎么说  对瑞秋而言
Hey,for what it's worth.. with Rachel,
我觉得你不可能只是一个随便的存在
I don't think you'll ever be just "anybody."
嘿  你用对场合了
Hey,there you go.
"谢谢"
"Thanks."
噢  天啊  她哭多久了
Oh,my God. How long has she been crying?
大约一个星期半
About a week and a half.
看起来你们都已经处理好了
Well,it looks like you guys got it under control,
所以我先回去了
so I'm just gonna go.
不好吗  不是吧
No? Really?
一定要有人共享悲惨命运吗
Misery really does love company?
好吧
All right.
试着用另一种方式抱她
Try holding her a different way.
二位  我已经竭尽全力了
You guys, I'm doing the best I can.
欢迎你们来试试看
Anyone else is welcome to try.
好吧  我来试试看
All right,I'll try. Fine.
-好了  好的  好的 -抱去吧
- Yes. Okay. Okay. - Here you go.
嘿  噢  天啊
Hey. Oh,gosh.
怎么抱都没用
Nothing works with this child!
天啊  我该怎么办呢
God,what am I gonna do,you guys?
我根本照顾不了我自己的孩子
I can't even comfort my own baby.
我是史上最糟的母亲
I'm the worst mother ever.
不  你只是初为人母罢了
No,you're just new at this.
会好起来的
You'll get better.
想想你第一天上班的时候
Think about your first day at work.
那也不是很简单的事
That couldn't have been easy,
但你也摆平了啊
but you figured that out.
是啊  我不认为穿得惹火一点
Yeah,I don't think dressing provocatively
对现在的情况会有帮助
is going to help me here!
天啊  请帮我抱一下
God,just please take her.
好  我来抱  来吧
Okay,I'll take her. Come on.
噢  天啊  我要去上一下厕所
Oh,boy,I have to go to the bathroom.
我要去枕头堆里吼一吼
I have to go scream into a pillow.
活泼  活泼的宝贝  活泼的宝贝
Bouncy. Bouncy baby. Bouncy baby.
噢  宝贝  宝贝  噢  宝贝  宝贝
Oh,baby,baby. Oh,baby,baby.
噢  宝贝  宝贝  宝贝
Oh,baby,baby,baby.
我聋了吗
Have I gone deaf?
有效了
It worked.
噢  宝贝  宝贝  宝贝
Oh,baby,baby,baby.
你在床上一定像个火球
You must be a fireball in bed!
我不敢相信  她睡着了
I can't believe it. She's asleep.
我让她睡着了
I got her to go to sleep.
我真的有神奇的魔力
I have actual magical powers.
我可以听到汽车跟鸟叫声
I can hear traffic and birds.
我又再度听到我脑海中的声音了
I can hear the voices in my head again.
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
噢  我的天  你让她不再哭了
Oh,my God! You got her to stop crying!
是的  我办到了
Yes,I did.
我是超级姑姑  莫妮卡
I'm Monica,super aunt.
你是官方认可的婴儿止哭专家
You are the official baby-crier stopper.
是啊  我正是
Yes,I am.
-你永远都不能离开这间公寓了 -什么
- You're never leaving the apartment. - Say what?
那是你的新工作  日夜兼顾
That's your new job,day or night.
只要她一哭  我就需要你在这里
She starts crying,I need you here.
不  不  不
No,no,no.
很庆幸  你一点都不需要我
Thankfully,you don't need me at all.
那么  嘿  超级姑姑 下次见啰
So okay. Hey,super aunt? See you later.
瑞秋  让她坚持6到8个月吧
Rachel? Let's give it six to eight months.
好的  听着  我要去睡一下
Okay,so listen,I'm gonna go lay down.
什么
What?
书上说只要她一睡  我也应该睡
The book says whenever she's sleeping,I should be sleeping.
所以
So..
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们才刚让她睡着
We just got her to go to sleep.
所以现在不能大声吼叫咯
So there can't be any yelling?
没错
No.
-我们要搬去塔尔萨了  -什么
- We're moving to Tulsa. - What?
我我听不到
I can't.. I can't hear.
-嘿  -嘿  你去哪了
- Hey. - Hey. Where have you been?
发生什么事了
What happened to you?
我跟乔伊打了起来
I had a little thing with Joey.
如果你认为我伤得很重  你该看看乔伊的伤
If you think this is bad,you should see him.
不  罗斯  那可不妙
No,Ross,this is not good.
我们必须谈谈乔伊这件事  请坐下
We have to talk about this Joey thing. Please sit.
好了  你必须放下乔伊这件事
All right,you have got to get over this Joey thing.
好吗
Okay?
我从未真的想要嫁给乔伊  好吗
I never really wanted to marry Joey,okay?
好的
Okay.
你知道我真的很想很想要什么吗
You know what I really,really want?
什么
What,Rach?
我想要睡觉
I wanna sleep.
我想吃东西  我想洗澡
I wanna eat. I wanna take a shower.
我是说  在她醒来之前
I mean,before she wakes up,
否则我们又有的忙了
and we gotta do this all over again.
-没错 -因为我必须告诉你
- Right. - I mean,because I got news for you.
艾玛  一点都不好带
Emma: not easy.
正因此我才在你身边
Well,that's what I'm here for.
-你要我去哄她吗  -不  真的不用
- You want me to get that? - No,that's really okay.
-莫妮卡 -来了  来了  来了
- Monica? - Got it,got it,got it,got it.
我一直在想这事
I've been thinking about this.
而且我要告诉你  那不是我的错
And I gotta tell you,it's not my fault.
那是自然的本能反应
It's a natural instinct.
你们在说什么
What are you talking about?
正好  好吧  如果我这样你会怎么做
Great. Okay,what would you do if I did this?